<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Venue on PyCon Pune Blog</title>
    <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/tags/venue/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Venue on PyCon Pune Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016 All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 18:30:17 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pune.pycon.org/blog/tags/venue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>New venue for the main conference, PyCon Pune 2017</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/pycon-pune-new-venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 18:30:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/pycon-pune-new-venue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/blog/images/amanora.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Amanora The Fern&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the last week we found out that the auditorium of COEP will not be
available for the whole duration of PyCon Pune 2017. Due to the already
action-packed &lt;a href=&#34;https://pyconpune.talkfunnel.com/2017/schedule&#34;&gt;schedule&lt;/a&gt; we were unable to adjust our
schedule to meet the venue availability and we were forced to look for an
alternate venue at the last moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a lot of sleepless nights balancing budgets and tireless days running
around looking for an alternate venue, we are happy to announce that our new
venue for the main conference is &lt;em&gt;AMANORA THE FERN Hotels and Club&lt;/em&gt;, in Amanora
Park Town, Magarpatta Road, Hadapsar, Pune, 411028. They are a new and
beautiful club in Amanora Park Town who were happy to host us and we hope to
set up a memorable event with their help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know it is late as many have already booked their stay in Pune, but we had
no choice as we had exhausted all possibilities. As usual if you have any
difficulties in planning then please feel free to reach out to us and we will
try and help to the best of our abilities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>