<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PyCon Pune Blog</title>
    <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PyCon Pune Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016 All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 09:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pune.pycon.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Red Hat</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-redhat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Glad to announce &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redhat.com/&#34;&gt;Red Hat&lt;/a&gt; as our sponsor for PyCon Pune 2017. Thanks &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/RedHatSoftware&#34;&gt;@RedHatSoftware&lt;/a&gt; for supporting PyCon Pune 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/blog/images/redhat.png&#34; alt=&#34;Red Hat&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Register for PyCon Pune 2017 &lt;a href=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/registration/&#34;&gt;https://pune.pycon.org/registration/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Attend PyCon Pune 2017</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/why-you-should-attend-pycon-pune-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 14:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/why-you-should-attend-pycon-pune-2017/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;no-matter-you-re-new-or-old-to-python&#34;&gt;No matter you&amp;rsquo;re new or old to Python&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New to Python? Don&amp;rsquo;t know how to get started? No worries! You are in right place.
Yes you just read it right! PyCon is one of the best places to learn Python.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Old to Python? There will be various talks with deep knowledge and ideas to challenge you.
Finally, you have got a place to get people work on your project i.e, Dev Sprints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Beginner&amp;rsquo;s to Advanced, you&amp;rsquo;ll get it all at the PyCon Pune 2017 (February 16th - 19th).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;looking-for-developers&#34;&gt;Looking for Developers?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for developers for your engineering team then PyCon is the place where you will get the best and brighest people around the world who will hang out for around four days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;keynote-speakers&#34;&gt;Keynote Speakers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keynote is the major attraction of any conference. At PyCon Pune, there will be six Keynote speakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ncoghlan_dev&#34;&gt;Nick Coghlan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; works on software supply chain management tools for Red Hat, and has been a CPython core developer since 2005. Prior to joining Red Hat in June 2011, Nick spent over 12 years working as a software developer, system integrator and system architect in Australia&amp;rsquo;s aerospace &amp;amp; defence sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/HonzaKral&#34;&gt;Honza Kral&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a Python programmer and Django core developer – since he is scared of the bright and shiny world of browsers, designers, and users he prefers to stay buried deep in the infrastructure code and just provides others with tools to do the actual site-building. Since 2008 Honza has been building content web sites for fun and profit. During this time he discovered Elasticsearch which lead to him joining the company behind it in 2013 to work on the Python drivers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/_gnovi&#34;&gt;Praveen Patil&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Praveen has been Google Summer of Code alumnus (GSoC 2014, 2015 and 2016). He is also mentor for Google Code-In and proud Fedora volunteer. Actively involved in ExpEYES project (&lt;a href=&#34;http://expeyes.in&#34;&gt;http://expeyes.in&lt;/a&gt;), teacher training programs and in the free time develops e-content for National Repository of Open Educational Resources (NROER). Experimenting and exploring the use of Python to actively engage the students and help them visualize the concepts of science and maths and have better understanding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/warty&#34;&gt;John &amp;lsquo;warthog9&amp;rsquo; Hawley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is an infrastructure and systems software programmer/architect turned to the dark side, now building hardware and embedded software systems that run on them, and a Perl guy, declared a Python programmer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/terriko&#34;&gt;Terri Oda&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; gets paid to break things and tell people that they&amp;rsquo;re wrong, all in the name of making open source software more secure. Her work on GNU Mailman helps open source developers communicate, her work with the Python Software Foundation helps introduce students to open source as part of Google Summer of Code, and her work in web security earned her a PhD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/kcunning&#34;&gt;Katie Cunningham&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a Python developer who is also a regular speaker, teacher, and writer of technical books. When she&amp;rsquo;s not cursing at computers, Keynote, or poorly formatted chapters, she knits, sews, and secretly writes fantasy books. She is the CTO of Speak Agent, a company focused on helping kids learn English through games. There, she creates iPad apps, websites, and curses English grammar on a regular basis. Katie lives in the DC area with her husband, two kids, and two dogs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dev-sprints&#34;&gt;Dev Sprints&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Development Sprint is a key part of PyCon. If you are looking for project to get started, or if you are looking for people to get them work on your project, then Dev Sprints is the best place where people will get together face-to-face for up to two days of itensive learning, hacking and development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yes, if you do not want to miss this golden opportunity buy your ticket now &lt;a href=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/registration&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Hurry up because we are running out! :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Python Software Foundation</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-psf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-psf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Glad to announce &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.python.org/psf/&#34;&gt;Python Software Foundation&lt;/a&gt; as our sponsor for PyCon Pune 2017. Thanks &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/thepsf&#34;&gt;@ThePSF&lt;/a&gt; for supporting PyCon Pune 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/blog/images/psf-logo.png&#34; alt=&#34;Python Software Foundation&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Register for PyCon Pune 2017 &lt;a href=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/registration/&#34;&gt;https://pune.pycon.org/registration/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Katie Cunningham</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-katie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 20:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-katie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome &lt;a href=&#34;http://therealkatie.net&#34;&gt;Katie Cunningham&lt;/a&gt; as our keynote speaker for &lt;a href=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/&#34;&gt;PyCon Pune 2017&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katie Cunningham is a Python developer who is also a regular speaker,
teacher, and writer of technical books. When she&amp;rsquo;s not cursing at
computers, Keynote, or poorly formatted chapters, she knits, sews, and
secretly writes fantasy books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is the CTO of Speak Agent, a company focused on helping kids learn
English through games. There, she creates iPad apps, websites, and
curses English grammar on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katie lives in the DC area with her husband, two kids, and two dogs.
You can follow her on Twitter at &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/kcunning&#34;&gt;@kcunning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Register and meet Katie at PyCon Pune 2017 &lt;a href=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/registration/&#34;&gt;https://pune.pycon.org/registration/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Elastic</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-elastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-elastic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Glad to announce &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.elastic.co/&#34;&gt;Elastic&lt;/a&gt; as our sponsor for PyCon Pune 2017. Thanks &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/elastic&#34;&gt;@elastic&lt;/a&gt; for supporting PyCon Pune 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/blog/images/elastic.png&#34; alt=&#34;Elastic&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Register for PyCon Pune 2017 &lt;a href=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/registration/&#34;&gt;https://pune.pycon.org/registration/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 21:51:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PyCon Pune 2017, a gathering for the community using and developing the free
and open-source Python programming language is happening from 16-19th February
2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PyCon Pune 2017 will be the first year for the Pune Python community.
This conference is organized by the Python community for the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The registrations are open so buy yourself a ticket as soon as possible.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pune.pycon.org/registration/&#34;&gt;https://pune.pycon.org/registration/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meet you at PyCon Pune 2017&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>