<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on PyCon Pune Blog</title>
    <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on PyCon Pune Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016 All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 21:51:36 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Registration for the PyCon Pune 2018 is  now open.</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/registration-pycon-pune-2018-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 21:51:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/registration-pycon-pune-2018-open/</guid>
      <description>PyCon Pune, the conference that started its journey in 2017, has opened up the registrations for the 2018 version now.
You have the following ticket options for the conference which you can purchase from the registration page in our website:
 The Conference Ticket for ₹1700 grants you access to the main conference, 8th &amp;amp; 9th of February 2018. This ticket also includes a t-shirt of your preferred size.
 The Conference &amp;amp; Developer Sprints Ticket come at a price of ₹2500.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submit your talk for PyCon Pune 2018</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/call-for-proposal-is-open-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/call-for-proposal-is-open-now/</guid>
      <description>Talks, speakers are one of the primary reason to make a conference a success. PyCon Pune is happy to announce that the Call for Proposals, for its 2nd edition, PyCon Pune, 2018 is now open! It will remain open till 15th September 2017.
We welcome talks from all sphere of life, including education, upstream project contributions, industry, science, community, legal, government, anything related to Python and to the community in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new Mailing List for us</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/a-new-mailing-list-for-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 18:39:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/a-new-mailing-list-for-us/</guid>
      <description>PyCon Pune 2017 was a grand success. Now, its time to set the tune for PyCon Pune 2018.
Since our first endeavor it has always been a community driven event and we wish to be so. To promote the goal, Sayan Chowdhury has announced the call for the design volunteers, helping in building our 2018 website. To give a shape to our 2018 edition we, the community at large, need to communicate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New venue for the main conference, PyCon Pune 2017</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/pycon-pune-new-venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 18:30:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/pycon-pune-new-venue/</guid>
      <description>Over the last week we found out that the auditorium of COEP will not be available for the whole duration of PyCon Pune 2017. Due to the already action-packed schedule we were unable to adjust our schedule to meet the venue availability and we were forced to look for an alternate venue at the last moment.
After a lot of sleepless nights balancing budgets and tireless days running around looking for an alternate venue, we are happy to announce that our new venue for the main conference is AMANORA THE FERN Hotels and Club, in Amanora Park Town, Magarpatta Road, Hadapsar, Pune, 411028.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-microsoft/</guid>
      <description>Glad to announce Microsoft as our sponsor for PyCon Pune 2017. Thanks @Microsoft for supporting PyCon Pune 2017.
Register for PyCon Pune 2017 https://pune.pycon.org/registration/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Red Hat</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-redhat/</guid>
      <description>Glad to announce Red Hat as our sponsor for PyCon Pune 2017. Thanks @RedHatSoftware for supporting PyCon Pune 2017.
Register for PyCon Pune 2017 https://pune.pycon.org/registration/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Child care facility during PyCon Pune</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/child-care-facility/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 14:39:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/child-care-facility/</guid>
      <description>We are planning to provide child care facility during the conference. If you are coming down with your kids and want to avail the child care facility, then please fill up this form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Attend PyCon Pune 2017</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/why-you-should-attend-pycon-pune-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 14:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/why-you-should-attend-pycon-pune-2017/</guid>
      <description>No matter you&amp;rsquo;re new or old to Python New to Python? Don&amp;rsquo;t know how to get started? No worries! You are in right place. Yes you just read it right! PyCon is one of the best places to learn Python.
Old to Python? There will be various talks with deep knowledge and ideas to challenge you. Finally, you have got a place to get people work on your project i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Python Software Foundation</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-psf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-psf/</guid>
      <description>Glad to announce Python Software Foundation as our sponsor for PyCon Pune 2017. Thanks @ThePSF for supporting PyCon Pune 2017.
Register for PyCon Pune 2017 https://pune.pycon.org/registration/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Katie Cunningham</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-katie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 20:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-katie/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Katie Cunningham as our keynote speaker for PyCon Pune 2017.
Katie Cunningham is a Python developer who is also a regular speaker, teacher, and writer of technical books. When she&amp;rsquo;s not cursing at computers, Keynote, or poorly formatted chapters, she knits, sews, and secretly writes fantasy books.
She is the CTO of Speak Agent, a company focused on helping kids learn English through games. There, she creates iPad apps, websites, and curses English grammar on a regular basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Elastic</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-elastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/welcome-elastic/</guid>
      <description>Glad to announce Elastic as our sponsor for PyCon Pune 2017. Thanks @elastic for supporting PyCon Pune 2017.
Register for PyCon Pune 2017 https://pune.pycon.org/registration/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 21:51:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pune.pycon.org/blog/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello World,
PyCon Pune 2017, a gathering for the community using and developing the free and open-source Python programming language is happening from 16-19th February 2017.
PyCon Pune 2017 will be the first year for the Pune Python community. This conference is organized by the Python community for the community.
The registrations are open so buy yourself a ticket as soon as possible. https://pune.pycon.org/registration/
Meet you at PyCon Pune 2017</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>